本字幕由「泉水渗透进字幕组」制作
听写: Whisper     时轴: yojoU     翻译: yojoU & ChatGPT
写呀 写呀 写
Writing, writing, writing.
戴夫  让演员们下来做第一季的评估
Dave, send the actors down for their season one evaluations.
嗨 我叫丹哈萌 是NBC《废柴联盟》的创剧人
Hi, I'm Dan Harmon. I created NBC's Community.
《废柴联盟》今年的收视率起伏不定
Community's had its ups and downs this year.
收视高峰是我们接在《办公室》后播出的晚上
Its ups were the nights we followed 'The Office'
人们不小心忘了关电视
and people left their TVs on by accident.
剩下的都是收视低谷
Its downs were the rest of the season.
在这些低谷中 收视率波动的原因是什么
Within those downs, what are the reasons why we fluctuate?
收视率好坏的原因又是什么
What are the reasons for our victories and failures?
我们会通过一系列「演员评估」来找出答案
Well, we're going to find that out through a series of cast evaluations.
非常感谢你的到来
Thank you so much for coming in.
不客气
No problem.
现在到季终了 这是成功的一季
It's the end of the season and it's been a successful season.
非常成功
Very successful.
我们谈谈你和其他演员的关系吧
Let's talk about your relationships with the other cast
我们的对话内容不会外传
and this is not going to leave this room.
这只是我用来评估的辅助材料
This is just an aid for me to use.
我讨厌艾莉森（安妮）
I hate Alison.
你讨厌艾莉森
You hate Alison.
讨厌
Hate Alison.
她有什么让你不爽的地方
What is it about her that's bugging you?
她是个帮不上忙的妞
She's a girl that doesn't help.
我认为所有人最终都应该成为男人
I believe that all people should be men eventually.
让我们谈谈其他人吧
Let's talk about some of the others.
行
Okay.
乔尔（杰夫）
Joel.
很好
Great.
好
是个男的
Guy.
吉莉安（布雷塔）
Gillian.
她还有改进的空间
Room for improvement to her.
有改进空间
Room for improvement.
性别原因
Due to gender.
切维（皮尔斯）
Chevy.
男 没问题
Dude. Fine.
丹尼（阿布蒂）
Danny.
哥们
Dude.
伊薇特（雪莉）
Yvette.
我不确定
I'm not sure.
我只是问你们每个人几个问题  并且不会外传
I'm simply asking a few questions of each of you guys and it doesn't leave this room.
你们的回答不外传
Your responses.
好的
Okay.
那为啥摄像头在这
That's why the cameras are here?
是这样 我们可能会收录在第一季的DVD里
Well, we may put it on the first season DVD.
我们来谈谈唐纳德对你有意见这件事吧
Let's just talk about the fact that Donald has a problem with you.
尤其针对你和艾莉森
You and Alison in particular
他只说了你们是女性 其他没多说
he didn't get much more specific than the fact that you were women.
嗯
Yeah.
你想对此说些什么
Would you care to comment on it at all?
好吧  我想到“恶语相向”这个词
Well, abusive is a word that comes to mind.
从他的视角吗
On his end?
是的
Yes.
种族歧视 因为
Racist because...
他种族歧视
He's racist.
你注意到他没说伊薇特
Well, you noticed that he didn't say Yvette.
你说他对女性有意见 但他只评价了演员中的两个白女
You said women, but he only said the two white women in the cast.
我觉得他可能把伊薇特当成男人了
I think he might think that she's a man.
你和安妮这个角色截然不同
The character is different from you.
怎么个不同法
How?
显然  安妮比较保守
Obviously, she's a little more buttoned up.
确实
Yes.
你一直在网上做各种稀奇古怪的性感把戏
You've been on the internet doing all kinds of outlandishly sexualized shenanigans.
是的 你真的不喜欢那样
Yeah, you really don't like that.
不 我喜欢
No, I do.
你真的不喜欢
You really don't.
我不介意
I'm fine with it.
你想让我一直扮演安妮
You want me to be Annie all the time.
但我告诉你  丹·哈萌  我可是个演员
But let me tell you, Dan Harmon, I'm an actor.
作为医生  你介意快速诊断一下你的演员同事吗
Do you mind, as a doctor, if we could quickly go through your castmates?
可以
Yeah.
而且  这绝对不会传达给他们
And again, this doesn't get back to them in any way.
但我可能需要你提供和其他人一样的帮助
But I could use your help as much as anybody's.
伊薇特·妮可·布朗
Yvette Nicole Brown?
我猜
I don't know.
她可能得了红斑狼疮
She may have lupus.
她现在得了吗
She may have it now?
前期症状通常会在头发上表现出来
The prodromal symptoms tend to manifest in the hair.
我注意到她的头发长了一点
And I've noticed that her hair has grown a little bit.
所以当头发长了 她可能会死
So when the hair grows, she could be dying?
是的 我担心她
Yeah, I just worry.
这季拍下来 她的头发越来越毛躁
Her hair's been more frizzy throughout the season.
然后她开始咳嗽
And then she developed a cough.
你还记得你的试镜吗  还记得拿到这个角色的时候吗
Do you remember your audition? Do you remember getting the part?
你还记得那些日子吗
Do you remember those days?
我确实记得我的试镜
I do remember my audition.
当时有我和你还有德瓦  我给你试镜
It was me, you, and Deva, and I auditioned for you.
然后你对我说
And you said to me,
我能把你介绍给我的朋友吗
can I show you to my friends?
那是你对我说的第一句话
That was the first thing you said to me.
我说好 然后你把他们叫了进来 那就是我的试镜
And I was like, sure, and then you called them in, and that was my audition.
因为那件事 你在我心中留下了好印象 我觉得很贴心
And you had a soft spot in my heart because of that. I thought that was really sweet.
肯认为你得了红斑狼疮
Ken thinks you have lupus.
我们来谈谈你的不足之处  比如
Let's talk about the weaknesses on your part, which are --
看这儿 我的体重 我知道这是个问题
Let's see here, weight. I know that's an issue.
你知道的  体重变化是甲状腺的症状之一
You know, it's one of those things where I have a thyroid problem.
我不知道这上面有没有写
I don't know if that's listed anywhere.
我就写“甲状腺”三个字
I'll just write down the word thyroid.
好的
Great.
我对此也无能为力
I can't really do anything about that.
我能做的就是建议你吃个三明治
What I can do is suggest you eat a sandwich.
我们第一集的收视率是7.89
We had a 7.89 rating in the beginning.
嗯 那是数百万家庭
Well, that's millions of households.
真的吗
That's true?
是的 然后下降到...
Yeah, and then down to...
我裸体是在哪集
Where am I naked?
你在第17集全身赤裸
Episode 17, this is where you're naked.
知道了
I see, okay.
对你光屁股的反应是...
And the response to your naked ass...
是什么
What's that?
全年收视最低谷
Low point of all year.
电视机前的观众都被吓跑了
People running from their televisions.
我有另一种解读
I have a different theory.
我觉得收视率和你的个人卫生挂钩
I feel like this tracks your physical hygiene.
你回想下   第一集时你的样子几乎和现在一样
If you think about it, you started out the year almost looking like you do now.
然后第二集播出
Then the second episode hit,
因为你觉得自己是个人物了
because you were like, huge deal.
你的胡子从那时候开始疯长
That's when the beard started growing.
那时你开始穿那种看起来像是从流浪汉尸体上扯下来的衬衫
That is when you began wearing shirts that looked like you stripped them off of Drifter's corpse.
而且闻起来也那样
And smelled that way.
我希望你也能对同组演员进行同样程度的审查
I want you to level this amount of scrutiny also if you can on your castmates.
因为我们可以在下一年进行改进
Because we can make improvements for next year.
好吧 如果你不介意 我们对演员逐个评价一下吧
Well, let's go through cast member by cast member if you don't mind.
切维·切斯
Chevy, Chase.
正如我在其他采访中所说 我很高兴他还活着
As I've said in other interviews, I'm thrilled he's alive.
我认为切维还有改进的空间  他不要再死嚼剧本了
I think room for improvement on Chevy is he needs to stop analyzing the script so much.
不要再嚼了
He needs to stop reading it.
他真的想得太多了
He really overthinks it.
他记住了每个人的台词
He memorizes everyone's parts.
是的
Yeah.
是我的台词吗?
Was it my line?
我忘词了
I forgot the line.
你想让我说哪句词?
What's the line you wanted me to do?
现在到哪句了?
What are we doing?
你的台词
Your line.
我忘了该死的台词 好吗
I forgot the fucking line, all right?
我之前记得那句台词 我觉得你最好把那句去掉
I knew the line before. I think you ought to lose that line.
他甚至都没把他的台词读对
He didn't even read his line right.
哦 你说了词吗?
Oh, did you say it?
我甚至不知道你在这儿
I didn't even know you were here.
我这次会记住的 准备好了吗
I'll get it this time. Ready?
回到你们的位置
Get back to your places.
所有人
All of you.
和其他人相处得怎么样
How's it going with the others?
你知道 我真的不太清楚
You know, I don't know, really.
我并不怎么关注他们  但是
I don't pay much attention to them, but ...
在我看来  他们都相当不错
it seems to me that they're all pretty good.
但我认为乔尔带不动这部剧 真的
I don't think that Joel carries it, really.
我想那才是美中不足之处
I think that may be the weak area.
他的问题
Problems with him.
那么到了第二季
So going into a second season.
我会换掉乔尔
I would replace Joel.
行
Okay.
我们一直在尝试用不同的组合来磨合你们
We've been trying to use you guys in different combinations.
有没有谁比其他人让你更喜欢搭档?
Is there anybody that you've enjoyed working with more than others?
嗯 有的
Well, yeah.
切维与二人共同主演1986年西部喜剧片《神勇三蛟龙》
不得不说我很享受与马丁·肖特和史蒂夫·马丁合作
Yeah, I'd have to say I liked very much working with Martin Short and Steve Martin.
我在艾莉森和吉莉安的名字边都打了个大红叉
I've got a big red check next to Alison and Gillian.
切维对你来说 还好
Chevy though, fine. Not at all.
你们相处得很好
You guys are getting along.
不 那家伙...
No, that guy's a...
可能是最不种族主义的家伙
Probably like the least racist guy.
过于不种族主义了
To a fault.
有点极端了 就比如
To the fault where it's just like, oh,
我们说去吃中餐吧  然后他会走到汉堡王去
let's go get some Chinese food and he'll just walk into a Burger King.
对 因为他甚至都分辨不出区别
Because he can't even tell the difference.
他分不清
He can't even tell the difference.
我说  嘿 哥们 这是汉堡啊
It's just like, hey man, these are burgers.
他说  哦 没注意到
And he's like, I didn't notice.
然后我就破防了
And you're just like, god damn.
看着我们的收视率走势图 我看到
I look at this chart of our ratings and I see
看到了收视长虹的潜力
you know... a potential for success.
我没看到明显的滑铁卢
I don't see obvious failure.
无意冒犯  但我要为自己辩解一下
I don't mean to sound offensive, but I'm being a little defensive.
第18集的4.7收视率不是我的错
That was not my fault for the 4.7 on 18 to...
嗯 这集当然不是你的错
Well, this certainly wasn't your fault.
你没在第一集中 你是在这集出场的
You weren't in this episode. You joined us here.
在试播集中 你扮演的是个正直 高尚 有责任心的角色
In the pilot, you're supposedly this honest, noble-hearted, conscientious kind of character.
是的
Yeah.
你的人设是在层层递进呢 还是在逐渐崩坏呢
Are we peeling back layers or are we changing the character?
两者都有一点吧
A little bit of both, I think.
当揭开角色的层层面纱 会发现
As we peel back these layers we'll find...
错了 我刚说错了
Wrong answer. I gave the wrong answer.
布雷塔是不是越来越像你了
Is she becoming more like you, the actor?
我觉得 我比布雷塔更...傻?
I think, sillier than Britta.
我察觉到了你的一些傻劲  不得不让你献丑了
I had to put you on the spot because I see some of the silliness.
哦 没事
Oh, sure.
她会 这样做 哇喔喔喔喔～
She's like, just like, whoaoooooo~
还有这样
Like that.
吉莉安和我有一场戏  那是在深夜
Gillian and I had that scene together. It was late at night.
我看着她的眼睛 即使她不在镜头前 她也给了我很多情感
And I looked in her eyes, and even when she wasn't on camera, she gave me so much emotion.
我感受到了布雷塔对雪莉的感情
Like, I felt Britta feeling for Shirley.
所以 我不可能不为她而挺身而出
So there was no way that I couldn't rise to the occasion for her
当她在镜头外给了我那么多支持的时候
when she was giving me so much off-camera.
很多演员不会这样做的
And a lot of actors don't do that.
她演得很自然
She's amazing in that natural way.
很棒
Amazing.
如果你和她拍真情流露的戏 会很完美
If you're doing a natural scene with her, it's perfect.
她会让你演得更好
She makes you better.
然后一旦她试图开玩笑  整段垮掉
And then as soon as she tries to do a joke, everything crumbles.
她是一个令人愉快的...
She is a delightful...
你知道吗 这是我觉得吉莉安还没表现出来的东西
You know what it is? This is what I think has not happened with Gillian.
我认为人们不知道她有多傻
I don't think people know how goofy she is.
现在这部剧开始更多地展现她有多傻
And now that the shows are starting to go more in how goofy she is,
我觉得她在那方面的喜剧才华真的会让人惊艳
I think her comedic talent in that area is about to really go, wow.
我知道你告诉过我你不在电视上看这部剧
I know you've told me you don't watch the show on television.
是的 我没电视机
No, I don't have a television.
然后你断言这并不是为了给我留下深刻印象
And then you assert that that is not an attempt to impress me.
这是千真万确的
This is honest truth.
我和我在东部的朋友们聊天时
People who I speak with who are my friends back East say that
他们都说这部剧每集都越来越好
the show is getting progressively better.
每一集
Every show.
这些人 我真的... 现在我说真的
And these are people I really... And now I'm being serious.
这些人我真的很信任 他们有很棒的喜剧感和视角
These are people I really trust who have great comic sensibilities and perspective.
是谁说的 是名人吗
Who said? Who's saying? Famous people?
不是 都是无名之辈
No. Nobody famous.
只是你欣赏的人
Just people that you admire.
是的 是好朋友
Yeah, good friends. Yeah.
实际上 其中一些是名人
Well, actually some of them are famous.
哈罗德·雷米斯 吗
Harold Ramis?
哈罗德·雷米斯很有名
Harold Ramis is famous.
好了
All right, well...
要结束了吗
We've got to wrap it up?
是的 你愿意再来一年吗
Yeah. Would you like to come back for another year?
愿意
Yeah.
当然 如果你愿意 我想我们明年给你留了个位置
Obviously, if you'd like to, I think we have a position for you next year.
今年和你一起工作真是太愉快了
It's been a pleasure to work with you this year.
我也是
You too.
你是我私底下最喜欢的之一
You're one of my favorites, secretly.
你会回来拍第二季的 我现在就告诉你
You're coming back for season two. I can tell you that right now.
大家都对你很满意
People are very happy with you.
是吗
Yeah?
我只是想确保你也开心
I just want to make sure that you're happy.
我非常开心 我从来没有这么多的时间被夺走过
I'm very happy. I've never had more time taken away from my life.
我想在第二季里为你的角色拓宽戏路
I want to try to find more things to do with your character in season two.
我认为我今年犯的最大错误之一是没有充分利用你
I think one of the biggest crimes I did this year is underutilize you.
我认为你是所有演员中最有才华的人
I think you're the most talented guy on the cast,
但我不能告诉其他人  因为...
and I can't tell that to any of the others because they're...
我是说 他人的才华同样让人感到不安
I mean, the same thing that makes them untalented makes them insecure.
我知道在第一年是这样的 你也知道
You know, I understand that it's this way in the first year,
当然 明年如果我出演的话
and, of course, next year, if I show up
拍摄可能会更顺利
things will probably go quicker.
大家都彼此熟悉了
People are used to each other.
我还是觉得把乔尔踢出去会进展得更顺利
And, again, with Joel out, I think things will move faster.
好吧 那么 非常感谢...
All right, fine. Well, thank you so much for...
这是我的荣幸 帕特里克
The pleasure was all mine, Patrick.
好
Yeah.
我的名字叫 丹
My name's Dan.
丹
Dan.
谢谢
Thank you.
感谢你来
Thanks for coming in.
也谢谢其他人的到来
And thank the others as well.
这真是让人大开眼界
That was very eye-opening.
希望你们喜欢
I hope you enjoyed it.
戴夫  你能砍了这部剧吗
Dave, could you please cancel the show?